<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CountryProfile</string>
    <string name="bangla_text">

The Tenth Commonwealth Women’s Affairs Ministers Meeting was held in Dhaka, 17–19 June 2013, with delegates from 30 countries and a theme of ‘Women’s Leadership for Enterprise’.

\n Muhammad Yunus, Founder of the Grameen Bank in Bangladesh, delivered the 6th Annual Commonwealth Lecture, on ‘Halving Poverty by 2015’, in 2003; he was awarded the Nobel Peace Prize in 2006, jointly with the Bank.

 \n Two Bangladeshi-born writers have won the Commonwealth Writers’ Prize Best First Book award: Adib Khan (1995) and Tahmima Anam (2008)
    </string>

    <string name="india_text">
        Many great empires were formed between 500 BC and AD 500. Notable among them were the Mauryas and the Guptas. This period saw major mathematical and astronomical advancements.
        many of which were ahead of their time and were rediscovered later in the West. In particular, Aryabhata theorised that the earth was a sphere that rotates about its axis and revolves around the sun. He also developed a calendar that is followed to this day.
        This period also saw a gradual decline of Buddhism and Jainism.
        The practice of Buddhism, in particular, disappeared from India
        sheartland, though Buddha himself was incorporated into the Hindu pantheon. Jainism continues to be practiced by a significant number who are ambivalent about whether they consider themselves Hindus or not. Hinduism itself went through significant changes. The importance of Vedic deities like Indra and Agni reduced and Puranic deities like Vishnu, Shiva, their various Avatars and family members gained prominence.

\n Akshardham Mandir, One of the biggest temples in India, Photo Courtesy : Wikipedia

\n Jamia Masjid, Delhi.
The Islamic conquest of India started in the 8th century. It was summed up by historian Will Durant in his famous line: “The Islamic conquest of India is probably the bloodiest story in history". Gradually the Islamic raiders started staying as the ruler, and soon many parts of North India was ruled by Islamic Sultanate specially in the Ganga
       and Yamuna valley. The most powerful of the
    </string>

    <string name="pakistan">
A virtual guide to the Islamic Republic of Pakistan a country in South Asia with a coastline on the Arabian Sea in south.
        \n Pakistan is bordered by Afghanistan, China, India, and Iran.

Within Pakistans landscape there is the flat fertile Indus plain in east,nurtured by the Indus,the countrys
        longest river and a key water resource.Pakistans
        north is mountainous. The nations highest mountains are in the Himalayas in north east.

    </string>
</resources>
